A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants and Program Files, 1982-2012; 1
  - Columbia University - Glied (20040180) - Task Force on Future of Health Insurance: Data Analysis and Technical Assistance, and Related Files, 2003-2004 (Box 359, Folder 1-7)
  - Columbia University - Glied (20040180) - Task Force on Future of Health Insurance: Data Analysis and Technical Assistance, and Related Files, 2003-2004 (Box 360, Folder 1-4)
  - Lake, Snell, Perry and Associates - Lake (20030502) - Health Care Focus Groups (Box 360, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University - Lambrew (2003449) - Informing State and Federal Debates on Major Health Reform, 2003-2006 (Box 360, Folder 6-8)
  - Kaiser Foundation Research Institute - Hsu (20050357) - Assessing the Impact of High Deductible Health Plans, 2005-2008 (Box 360, Folder 9-10)
  - Kaiser Foundation Research Institute - Hsu (20050357) - Assessing the Impact of High Deductible Health Plans, 2005-2008 (Box 361, Folder 1)
  - Independent Sector - Aviv (20060023), 2005-2006 (Box 361, Folder 2)
  - Independent Sector - Aviv (20060492) (Box 361, Folder 3)
  - Independent Sector - Aviv (20070360) (Box 361, Folder 4)
  - Independent Sector - Aviv (20080195) (Box 361, Folder 5)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - McGencey (20060497) (Box 361, Folder 6)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - McGencey (20070356), 2006-2007 (Box 361, Folder 7)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - McGencey (20080191) (Box 361, Folder 8)
  - Rutgers University - Cantor (20060405) - State Scorecard on Healthcare System Performance, Part 2, 2006-2005 (Box 361, Folder 9)
  - Rutgers University - Cantor (20060405) - State Scorecard on Healthcare System Performance, Part 2 - Background and Articles (Box 362, Folder 1)
  - Rutgers University - Cantor (20060405) - State Scorecard on Healthcare System Performance, Part 2 - Grant Products (Box 362, Folder 2)
  - Rutgers University - Cantor (20060405) - State Scorecard on Healthcare System Performance, Part 2 - Administration and Budget (Box 362, Folder 3)
  - Rutgers University - Cantor (20060405) - State Scorecard on Healthcare System Performance, Part 2 - Proposal Development (Box 362, Folder 4)
  - Book Program - Rockefeller University (90-09) (Box 365, Folder 2)
  - Book Program - University of Massachusetts, Boston - Bass (91-42) (Box 365, Folder 3)
  - Book Program - Westbroek (Box 365, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund - McGarvey (20020241), 2001-2002 (Box 366, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20010699), 2001-2002 (Box 366, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20000340), 1999-2003 (Box 366, Folder 3)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges - Longin (20030145), 2001-2003 (Box 366, Folder 4)
  - Utah Department of Health - Deily (20020591), 2002-2004 (Box 366, Folder 5)
  - Utah Department of Health - Deily (20010464), 2001-2004 (Box 366, Folder 6)
  - Utah Department of Health - Deily (20000381), 2000-2002 (Box 366, Folder 7)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health - Guyer (20010683), 2001-2008 (Box 367, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Beal (20010746) (Box 367, Folder 2)
  - Alliance to End Childhood Lead Poisoining - Guthrie (20000717), 2000-2001 (Box 367, Folder 3)
  - Kaiser Permanente Center for Health Research (20020694), 2002-2006 (Box 367, Folder 4)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20020418), 2002-2004 (Box 367, Folder 5)
  - Center for Health Care Strategies (20020487), 2002-2006 (Box 368, Folder 1)
  - Regents of the University of California - Halfon (20020383), 2002-2006 (Box 368, Folder 2)
  - State of Vermont, Agency of Human Services - Walllace-Brodeur (20020592), 2002-2003 (Box 368, Folder 3)
  - State of Vermont, Agency of Human Services - Walllace-Brodeur (20010463), 2001-2003 (Box 368, Folder 4)
  - State of Vermont, Agency of Human Services - Walllace-Brodeur (20000384), 1999-2001 (Box 368, Folder 5)
  - University of Wisconsin - Zimmerman (990499), 1999-2002 (Box 369, Folder 1-2)
  - Children's Hospital - Nugent (20000135), 2000-2001 (Box 369, Folder 3)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20010387), 2000-2002 (Box 369, Folder 4)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - NASHP - Riley (20000419), 2000-2002 (Box 369, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina - Department of Health and Human Services - Perruzzi (20000382), 1999-2001 (Box 370, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina - Department of Health and Human Services - Perruzzi (20010446), 2001-2002 (Box 370, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina - Department of Health and Human Services - Yaeger (20020593) (Box 370, Folder 3)
  - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20010583), 2001-2003 (Box 370, Folder 4)
  - Darmouth College - Olson (20031304), 2003-2007 (Box 370, Folder 5)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Vladeck (20020552), 2002-2006 (Box 370, Folder 6)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (20020542), 2002-2004 (Box 371, Folder 1)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (20020646), 2002-2005 (Box 371, Folder 2)
  - International Communications Research - Herrmann (20040176), 2003-2005 (Box 371, Folder 3)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (20020096), 2001-2004 (Box 371, Folder 4)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Stein (200020004), 2001-2002 (Box 371, Folder 5)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20030146), 2002-2004 (Box 371, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University School of Public Health - Glied (980494), 1998-1999 (Box 371, Folder 7)
  - Harvard University - Kennedy School of Government - Zimmerman (990796), 1999-2003 (Box 371, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University - Bergman (20040730), 2004-2006 (Box 372, Folder 1)
  - Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health - Guyer (20030197), 2002-2006 (Box 372, Folder 2)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine - Sturner (20010237), 2000-2002 (Box 372, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut Children's Medical Center - Dworkin (20030666), 2003-2006 (Box 372, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University - Mailman School - McLearn (20020183), 2001-2008 (Box 372, Folder 5)
  - Child Trends, Inc. (20030340), 2003-2005 (Box 373, Folder 1)
  - UCLA - Kuo (20030314), 2003-2007 (Box 373, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services - Sims (20020428), 2002-2005 (Box 373, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (980885 PDF) - Quality Indicators Meeting (Box 373, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (990819) - International Symposium 2000, 2000-2001 (Box 373, Folder 5)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - Leatherman (20020658), 2002-2006 (Box 373, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Health Quality Partners - Karp (20010648) (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - The Leapfrog Group for Patient Safety (20020699), 2002-2006 (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Needleman (20020510), 2002-2004 (Box 374, Folder 3)
  - Harris Interactive - Zapert (20020414), 2001-2005 (Box 374, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown - Summer (20030559), 2003-2004 (Box 374, Folder 5)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation - Bellevue Hospital - Hessler (20040868), 2004-2010 (Box 375, Folder 1)
  - Bellevue Hospital - Hessler (20080053), 2007-2010 (Box 375, Folder 2-5)
  - University of Rochester - Epstein (200090289), 2008-2010 (Box 375, Folder 6)
  - University of California - Rittenhouse (20100009), 2009-2010 (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center - Jaen (20090673), 2009-2010 (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - National Opition Research Center (NORC) - Gabel (20080455), 2008-2009 (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Fanning (20090273) (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown - Summer (20070057), 2006-2007 (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Warren - Declined (20080490) (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Education and Research Fund, EBRI -Fronstin (20090027), 2008-2010 (Box 376, Folder 7)
  - AcademyHealth - Collins (20070548) (Box 376, Folder 8)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute - Salisbury (20050015), 2004-2005 (Box 376, Folder 9)
  - University of Minnesota - Abraham (20050726), 2006-2010 (Box 377, Folder 1-6)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) - Fronstin (20070223), 2006-2007 (Box 377, Folder 7)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) - Fronstin (20060444), 2006-2007 (Box 377, Folder 8)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) - Fronstin (200700731), 2007-2008 (Box 377, Folder 9)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) - Fronstin (20070463), 2007-2008 (Box 377, Folder 10)
  - Research Foundation of SUNY - Andrulis (20020060), 2001-2003 (Box 377, Folder 11)
  - Research Foundation of SUNY - Andrulis (20020060), 2001-2003 (Box 378, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Pilgrim Health Care - Soumerai (20060449), 2006-2007 (Box 378, Folder 2-6)
  - Harvard Pilgrim Health Care - Soumerai (20060449) - Grant Products, 2006-2007 (Box 379, Folder 1-2)
  - JSI Research and Training - Davidson (20020198), 2001-2005 (Box 379, Folder 3-7)
  - National Opinion Research Center (NORC) - Gabel (20070444), 2007-2008 (Box 379, Folder 8)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) - Fronstin (20050506), 2005-2006 (Box 379, Folder 9)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) - Fronstin (20050506), 2005-2006 (Box 380, Folder 1-2)
  - Center for Studying Health System Change - Gabel (20050290), 2004-2007 (Box 380, Folder 3-5)
  - The Lewin Group - Sheils (20060596), 2006-2007 (Box 380, Folder 6-7)
  - Health Policy Research and Development (HPDR) - Horton (20060595), 2006-2007 (Box 380, Folder 8-9)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20060349), 2006-2007 (Box 381, Folder 1-3)
  - The Center for Effective Philanthropy - Buchanan (20080243) (Box 381, Folder 4)
  - The Center for Effective Philanthropy - Bolduc (20060072), 2006-2008 (Box 381, Folder 5)
  - The Center for Effective Philanthropy - Bolduc (20050719), 2005-2006 (Box 381, Folder 6)
  - Association of Health Care Journalists - Voss (20040514) (Box 381, Folder 7)
  - Association of Health Care Journalists - Voss (20030471) (Box 381, Folder 8)
  - Association of Health Care Journalists - Bruzzese (20090356), 2008-2010 (Box 381, Folder 9)
  - Association of Health Care Journalists - Bruzzese (20080203) (Box 381, Folder 10)
  - Association of Health Care Journalists - Bruzzese (20070653), 2007-2008 (Box 381, Folder 11)
  - Association of Health Care Journalists - Bruzzese (20070112), 2006-2007 (Box 381, Folder 12)
  - Association for Health Services - Helms (990476), 1999 (Box 381, Folder 13)
  - American Society on Aging - Kleyman (20080131) (Box 381, Folder 14)
  - American Society on Aging - Kleyman (20070292) (Box 381, Folder 15)
  - American Public Media - Gossett (20070544) (Box 382, Folder 1)
  - American Medical Association - Flanagin (20060019) (Box 382, Folder 2)
  - Alliance for Health Reform (20040178) (Box 382, Folder 3)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20080352) (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20080189) (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20070354) (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20060487) (Box 382, Folder 7)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20050429), 2005-2006 (Box 382, Folder 8)
  - Foundation Center - Engelhardt (20070355) (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - Foundation Center - Engelhardt (20060488) (Box 383, Folder 2)
  - Foundation Center - Engelhardt (20080190) (Box 383, Folder 3)
  - International Society for Quality in Health Care - Tregloan (20070396) (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - International Society for Quality in Health Care - Boland (20080196) (Box 383, Folder 5)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - Kreinin (20070361) (Box 383, Folder 6)
  - Center for Excellence in Health Care Journalism - Bruzzese (20060278) (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - Center for Excellence in Health Care Journalism - Holtz (20050510) (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - Seltzer (20060493) (Box 383, Folder 9)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Clark (20070362) (Box 384, Folder 1)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20060490) (Box 384, Folder 2)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20040431), 2005 (Box 384, Folder 3)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20070358) (Box 384, Folder 4)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20080193) (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20080192), 2008-2009 (Box 384, Folder 6)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20050430) (Box 384, Folder 7)
  - Mayor's Fund to Advance New York City - Cadogan (20040080), 2003-2007 (Box 384, Folder 8)
  - Mayor's Fund to Advance New York City - Cadogan (20040080), 2003-2007 (Box 385, Folder 1-5)
  - Montefiore Medical Center - Racine (20040852), 2003-2010 (Box 385, Folder 6-10)
  - MetroPlus Health Plan - Saperstein (20040160), 2003-2010 (Box 386, Folder 1-8)
  - Society of American Business Editors and Writers (20090510) (Box 386, Folder 9)
  - Society of American Business Editors and Writers - Paden (20080133) (Box 386, Folder 10)
  - Society of American Business Editors and Writers - Paden (20070414) (Box 386, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller University - Stapleton - Rockefeller Archive Center (20070588) (Box 387, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University - Stapleton - Rockefeller Archive Center (20060640) (Box 387, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller University - Levold - Rockefeller Archive Center (20080353) (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - Project Hope - Dentzer (20080474) (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Project Hope - Dentzer (20080151) (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Project Hope - Dentzer (20070363) (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Project Hope - Howe (20060409) (Box 387, Folder 7)
  - Primary Care Development Corp. - Kotelchuck (20080202) (Box 387, Folder 8)
  - Philanthropy New York - Brown (20090447) (Box 387, Folder 9)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - Brown (20080197) (Box 387, Folder 10)
  - Nonprofit Facilities Fund - Miller (95-26), 1995-2001 (Box 387, Folder 11)
  - Nonprofit Facilities Fund - Miller (95-26), 1995-2001 (Box 388, Folder 1-4)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Clark (20090448) (Box 389, Folder 1)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Clark (20080198) (Box 389, Folder 2)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Boufford (20080414) (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - National Public Radio (20040809) (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - National Business Coalition on Health - Webber (20090274) (Box 389, Folder 5)
  - National Hispanic Medical Association - Rios (20090241) (Box 389, Folder 6)
  - Morehouse School of Medicine - Davis (20080083) (Box 389, Folder 7)
  - Leading Age - Stone (20070611) - Organizational Readiness and Implementation Guide Revision (Box 401, Folder 1-2)
  - Bowers (20030672) - Wellspring Implementation Manual (Box 401, Folder 3)
  - Bowers (23246) (Box 401, Folder 4)
  - Planetree - Gil (20100520) - Developing Systems to Support Person-Centered Care (Box 401, Folder 5)
  - Planetree - Gil (20100520) - Developing Systems to Support Person-Centered Care (Box 402, Folder 1)
  - Fleetwood Project - Pharmacist Materials (Box 402, Folder 2-5)
  - Brown University - Lapane (20010695) - Evaluating the Impact of Perspective Drug Management on Medication Related Problems in Long-Term Care: The Fleetwood Model, 2001-2012 (Box 402, Folder 6)
  - Brown University - Lapane (20010695) - Evaluating the Impact of Perspective Drug Management on Medication Related Problems in Long-Term Care: The Fleetwood Model, 2001-2012 (Box 403, Folder 1-6)
  - Brown University - Lapane (20010695) - Evaluating the Impact of Perspective Drug Management on Medication Related Problems in Long-Term Care: The Fleetwood Model, 2001-2012 (Box 404, Folder 1-4)
  - University of Minnesota - Kane (20060167) - Full-Scale Implementation and Sustainability of Small-Group Nursing Homes in Tupelo, MS: Lessons for Replication, 2005-2007 (Box 405, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Minnesota - Kane (20030501) - Evaluation of Small Group Homes for Nursing Home Residents, 2003-2006 (Box 405, Folder 3-4)
  - University of Minnesota - Kane (20030501) - Evaluation of Small Group Homes for Nursing Home Residents, 2003-2006 (Box 406, Folder 1-6)
  - University of Minnesota - Kane (20030501) - Evaluation of Small Group Homes for Nursing Home Residents, 2003-2006 (Box 407, Folder 1-2)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Assessing State Medicaid Cost Containtment Strategies (6182), 1982-1984 (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth Fund History (Box 423, Folder 1-5)
  - Mixed Blessings Manuscript, 1985-1986 (Box 424, Folder 1-3)
  - Before It's Too Late: The Child Guidance Movement, 1921-1945 - Horn - Manuscript, 1984 (Box 424, Folder 4-6)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Casarett (20000707), 2000-2001 (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Edelman (20010274) - Enforcement, Monthly Mailings (Box 425, Folder 2)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Casarett (20000707), 2000-2002 (Box 425, Folder 3)
  - Center for Medicare Advocacy - Edelman (20010274) - Enforcement, Monthly Mailings (Box 425, Folder 4-7)
  - Columbia University - Leiman (980207) - Symposium on Women's Health, Phase 2, 1997-2001 (Box 426, Folder 1-2)
  - Columbia University - Leiman (96626) - Commission on Women's Health, 1996-1999 (Box 426, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University - Klitzman (97065), 1996-2000 (Box 426, Folder 4)
  - Barnes Hospital - Billington (94-32), 1993-1996 (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Association for Health Services Research - Hersh (970941) - Program Direction, Picker-Commonwealth Fund Scholars Program 1997-1998 (Box 427, Folder 2-4)
  - Albert Einstein Medical Center - Bernstein (96027) - Youth Mentoring Program, 1995-1997 (Box 428, Folder 1)
  - Iowa Methodist Medical Center - Black (96993) - Youth Mentoring Program, 1995-1997 (Box 428, Folder 2)
  - Iowa Methodist Medical Center - Black (94-123) - Youth Mentoring Program, 1994 (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Iowa Methodist Medical Center - Black (96026) - Youth Mentoring Program, 1995-1996 (Box 428, Folder 4)
  - The Investment Fund for Foundations - Salem (95-28), 1994-1998 (Box 428, Folder 5)
  - Outward Bound Program - Instructor Survey, 1988 (Box 428, Folder 6)
  - Outward Bound Program - Project Director Survey, 1988 (Box 428, Folder 7)
  - Outward Bound Program - Grant (10237), 1987-1988 (Box 428, Folder 8)
  - Outward Bound Program - Student Survey, 1988 (Box 428, Folder 9)
  - Outward Bound Program - Surveys, 1988 (Box 429, Folder 1)
  - Saving Lives Program - Development, 1986-1988 (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - Saving Lives Program, 1988 (Box 429, Folder 3)
  - Saving Lives Program - Management Meeting, 1989 May (Box 429, Folder 4)
  - Saving Lives Program - Program Review, 1989 September 8 (Box 429, Folder 5)
  - Living-At-Home Program - Non-Fund Supported Sites, 1988 (Box 430, Folder 1)
  - Living-At-Home Program - New York Hospital (8877), 1986-1988 (Box 430, Folder 2)
  - Living-At-Home Program - Program Evaluation (8877), 1986-1988 (Box 430, Folder 3-4)
  - Living-At-Home Program - Program Evaluation (8877), 1986-1988 (Box 431, Folder 1)
  - Living-At-Home Program - Selection of Grantees, 1983-1986 (Box 431, Folder 2)
  - Living-At-Home Program - Press Media, 1985-1988 (Box 431, Folder 3)
  - Living-At-Home Program - Advisory Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 431, Folder 4)
  - Living-At-Home Program - Board Authorization, 1984-1986 (Box 431, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (970952) - Academic Health Centers - Administration and Budget (Box 432, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (970952) - Academic Health Centers - Correspondence (Box 432, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (970952) - Academic Health Centers - Articles and Background (Box 432, Folder 3)
  - Jacobs Institute - Romans (20000181) - Second Annual Commonwealth Fund Conference on Women's Health (Box 432, Folder 4)
  - Jacobs Institute - Romans (20000181) - Second Annual Commonwealth Fund Conference on Women's Health - Grant Products (Box 432, Folder 5)
  - Jacobs Institute - Romans (20000181) - Second Annual Commonwealth Fund Conference on Women's Health - Administration and Budget (Box 432, Folder 6)
  - Jacobs Institute - Romans (20000181) - Second Annual Commonwealth Fund Conference on Women's Health - Correspondence (Box 432, Folder 7)
  - Jacobs Institute - Romans (20000181) - Second Annual Commonwealth Fund Conference on Women's Health - Articles and Background (Box 432, Folder 8)
  - Jacobs Institute - Romans (20000181) - Second Annual Commonwealth Fund Conference on Women's Health (Box 432, Folder 9)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (990257) - The Future of the Educational Mission of New York Academic Health Centers, 1998-1999 (Box 432, Folder 10)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (20000163) - The Doctor at the Millenium: Practice in A Changing Environment (Box 433, Folder 1)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (970598), 1996-1999 (Box 433, Folder 2)
  - National Health Law Program, Inc. - Lavin (990349) (Box 433, Folder 3)
  - United Hospital Fund (96920) - State Strategies for Financing Graduate Medical Education, 1996-1997 (Box 433, Folder 4)
  - Duke University - Snyderman (Box 433, Folder 5)
  - New York University (NYU) - Blustein (20000099) (Box 433, Folder 6)
  - The Carter Center - Hardman (990862) (Box 433, Folder 7)
  - Nuffield Trust - Owen (990218) - Annual Margaret E. Mahoney Symposium 1999 - Administration and Budget (Box 433, Folder 8)
  - Nuffield Trust - Owen (990218) - Annual Margaret E. Mahoney Symposium 1999 - Correspondence (Box 433, Folder 9)
  - Nuffield Trust - Owen (990218) - Annual Margaret E. Mahoney Symposium 1999 - Papers (Box 433, Folder 10)
  - Nuffield Trust - Owen (990218) - Annual Margaret E. Mahoney Symposium 1999 - Papers (Box 434, Folder 1)
  - Harvard University - Siegel (20020085) - Fellowship Program Evaluation, 2001-2003 (Box 434, Folder 2)
  - Medicare Rights Center - Beebe (20050310), 2004-2006 (Box 434, Folder 3)
  - Medicare Rights Center - Beebe (20050310) - Grant Products, 2004-2006 (Box 434, Folder 4)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (20020646) - Grant Products, 2002-2004 (Box 434, Folder 5)
  - Wellspring Innovative Solutions - Kehoe - Raetzman (20000710) - Authorization (Box 435, Folder 1)
  - American Society on Aging - Kleyman (20060279), 2005-2006 (Box 435, Folder 2)
  - AcademyHealth - Pittman (20040494) (Box 435, Folder 3)
  - DOCTalk - Salazar (20090237), 2008-2009 (Box 435, Folder 4)
  - American Society on Aging - Anderson (20090321) (Box 435, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University - Pardes (20000364), 1999-2000 (Box 435, Folder 6)
  - Elmhurst Hospital Center - Edwards (96032), 1995-2000 (Box 435, Folder 7)
  - Tiranoff Productions - Tiranoff (20090134), 2008-2009 (Box 435, Folder 8)
  - AcademyHealth - Martinez-Vidal (20060636), 2005-2006 (Box 435, Folder 9)
  - AcademyHealth - Adams (20060624), 2006-2007 (Box 435, Folder 10)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20050487), 2005-2006 (Box 435, Folder 11)
  - AcademyHealth - Guterman (20070532), 2007-2009 (Box 435, Folder 12)
  - AcademyHealth - Stuart (20060623), 2005-2007 (Box 435, Folder 13)
  - AcademyHealth - Guterman (20050633), 2005-2006 (Box 435, Folder 14)
  - Commonwealth Fund - IHP Sessions at the Annual Meeting of the Academy for Health Services Research and Policy (20000706) (Box 435, Folder 15)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn and Anderson (20000471) (Box 435, Folder 16)
  - Healthy Steps - McLearn (20000506) - Authorization (Box 436, Folder 1)
  - International Health Policy - Osborn (970665), 1997-1998 (Box 436, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University - School of Public Health - Coker (980672) - Harkness Fellowships Extention, 1998 (Box 436, Folder 3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020694) (Box 436, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020694) - Grant Products (Box 436, Folder 5)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020694) - Correspondence (Box 436, Folder 6)